我们,是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
毫无保留
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
presisco
校对
Husky
特效
presisco
压制
这本能够...
That could have gone...
变得糟糕很多的
A lot worse.
也可能变得好很多的
Could have gone a lot better, too.
史蒂文，我收到了你的留言
Steven, I got your message.
史蒂文？
Steven?
发生了什么？
What happened?!
我们赢了！
We won!
那是紫晶吗？
Is that Amethyst?
呃...一切还好吗？
Uh, what -- what's going on?
你说出现了巨大太空手掌一类的东西
You said there's some kind of giant space hand
而你们可能都得死？
and you all might die?
康妮！你不会相信到底发生了什么！
Connie! You're not going to believe what happened!
我该怎么开头呢？
Where do I even start?
这里真是疯人院一般啊！
It's been a madhouse over here!
紫晶！闹够了没！
Amethyst! That's enough celebrating!
史蒂文！
Steven!
爸爸！
Dad!
康妮，我得挂了，我保证我会打给你的
Connie, I have to go. I promise I'll call you back.
爸爸回来了！爸爸回来了！
Dad's back! Dad's back!
噢！感谢上帝！你没事！
Oh! Thank goodness! You're okay!
我看到太空船开始起飞，
I saw the spaceship start to leave,
然后又坠毁在这里，然后我返回这里，然后--
and then it crashed, and I came back, and --
恶！你的眼睛
uggggh! Your eye.
但你没什么大碍！
But you're okay!
我想那些混蛋们根本比不上水晶战士
I guess those jerks were no match for The Crystal Gems.
不可能 ！她们超级碉！
No way! They were superstrong!
但你还是想方法打败了她们？
But you were able to beat them back?
不，她们实力碾压我们！
No. They totally stomped us!
有个铁石英战士超级粗壮
This warrior Jasper was super-beefy
直接把我砸晕了
and knocked me unconscious.
然后她们将我绑架上船
Then they abducted me onto the ship
因为她们想带走我
because they wanted to take me away forever.
接着我们让飞船坠毁了，我也差点挂了！
And then we crashed the ship, and I almost died!
她们到底想拿你怎么样？
What did they want with you?
她们认为我是妈妈
They think I'm mom.
有-有更多的母世界宝石人会在找你？
A-are more homeworld gems gonna come after you?
我--呃...
I -- uh...
我不知道，也许会？
I don't know. Maybe?
史蒂文，我非常支持你并为你感到骄傲，
Steven, I'm supportive and very proud of you,
而且我马上就会回来
and I'll be right back.
一定要淡定
Got to calm down.
我的--
Where's my --
我的放松CD在哪？
where's my relaxing-music cd?!
这个？
This one?
不是！
Wrong one!
暂停！弹出！
Stop! Eject!
现在，康妮，千万别发疯啊，
Now, Connie, please don't freak out,
但一个巨大的激光手试图将我绑架到太空
but a giant laser hand tried to steal me into space.
但它没得逞，它没得逞
But it didn't. It didn't.
我回来了，而且目前一切安...好
I'm back, and everything is f-fine...Now.
嗯，康妮，有趣的是--我发现，
Um, Connie, funny story -- as it turns out,
宝石人的数量远远超过我们的想象
there's a lot more gems out there than we thought,
而我觉得他们想...杀了我？
And I think they want to... Kill me?
嘿，康妮，那-那个我留给你的信息
Hey, Connie, that -- that message I left you
只是--只是个梦
was -- was just a dream.
呃，这糊弄不了她
Eh, she's too smart for that.
噢，嘿，罗纳多
Oh. Hey, Ronaldo.
你没听说吗？
Didn't you hear?
杜威市长号召每个人回到沙滩市
Mayor Dewey's calling everyone back into the city.
我们现在可以回家了
We can go home now.
噢，我知道了
Oh. I see.
你也是来这里沉思啊！
You come up here to brood, too!
沉思？
Brood?
没错，史蒂文
Yes, Steven.
那正是人们想让我们做的--
That's just what people like us do --
默默承受，
suffer quietly,
担负起其他人无法担负的认知
shouldering the knowledge no one else can bear.
你自己作为“异常”的爱好者，
As an aficionado of "the weird" yourself,
可能已经注意到大众害怕
you've probably noticed ordinary people fear
冰冷，沉重的真相
the cold, leaded anchor of the truth.
这深渊可不是闹着玩的
The abyss is no Sunday swan ride.
我知道！我爸爸在知道真相后疯掉了！
I know! My dad flipped out when I told him!
听起来很正常
Sounds typical.
但这是个非常好的提醒
But it's a good reminder.
我们所选择的路并不容易
This is no easy path we've chosen here.
经常有...
There are...
牺牲
Sacrifices.
看看下面那些人，史蒂文
Look at them all down there, Steven.
这是我们的使命，让那些简单的人
It's our duty to let those simple people
过着简单的生活
live out their simple lives
无需了解与我们为友的负担
without ever knowing the burden of being friends with us.
至少我们可以相互支持
At least we can be there for each other.
那是个从天而降的巨掌
Is that giant hand from the sky
躺在沙滩正中吗？
sitting right in the middle of the beach?!
我得把这个发到博客上去！
I got to get some of this for my blog!
每人都说宝石事物危险
♪ Everybody told me gem stuff's dangerous ♪
我猜我一直不信，直到现在
♪ I guess I didn't believe it until now ♪
爸爸总是非常善解人意
♪ dad always seemed apprehensive ♪
而现在变得非常害怕
♪ and now he's really freaking out ♪
我该如何？
♪ what do I do?
我不想让你被影响
♪ I don't want that for you
每人都说生命非常宝贵
♪ Everybody tells me life is precious ♪
都在这地球
♪ on the planet earth
当然包括你，我必须要保护你
♪ and that means you, and I have to protect you ♪
如果你受到伤害
♪ what if somehow you get hurt? ♪
我该如何？
♪ What do I do?
我不想你被影响
♪ I don't want that for you
♪ ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
我该如何告诉你？
♪ What am I going to tell you?
你最好不知道我身陷的麻烦
♪ You're better off not knowing the trouble I'm in ♪
我不希望你担忧
♪ I don't want you to worry
担忧我所见，担忧我所至
♪ about what I've just seen, about where I've just been ♪
你不用涉及到这其中
♪ you don't have to be a part of this ♪
我不认为我想这样
♪ I don't think I want you to be ♪
你不需要
♪ you don't need this
你不需我
♪ you don't need me
♪ ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
嗷，别呀！
Aww, come on!
不要抱怨，我们得开始清理残骸了
No whining. We need to start cleaning up the debris.
石榴说的对
Garnet's right.
人类已经开始返回镇上了
People are already coming back into town.
我们得让他们远离沙滩
We've got to keep them off the beach.
如果任何人类有机会接触到宝石科技，
If any humans got access to gem technology,
他们很可能会伤害到自己
they could really hurt themselves.
也许我们该一劳永逸的将他们拦在外面
Maybe we should shut them out for good.
你要知道，我们的确设置过围栏
You know, we did once have a fence.
那再建个新的吧--带倒刺的那种！
Let's get a new one -- with barbed wire!
这次，让我们修个护城河
This time, let's build a moat.
我可以当...
I could be...
鳄鱼精！
♪ The crocodile!
爵士手
Jazz hands.
不
No.
为什么不呢？
Why not?!
你总是说你要成为鳄鱼精，
You always say you'll be the crocodile,
但你从没做到过
but you never commit.
也不用围栏
No fence, either.
石～榴！
Garnet!
史蒂文得能见到他的父亲和朋友
Steven needs to see his father and his friends.
不，我不用
No, I don't!
我不能总是放不下我人性的那部分
I can't keep clinging to the vestiges of my humanity.
我是时候严肃点了
It's time I got serious.
史蒂文，为什么你的通讯设备
Steven, why is your communication device
播放那个音乐？
playing that song?
是康妮的电话
It's Connie trying to call me.
但我不能再与她见面了
But I can't face her anymore.
那么...你就打算永远忽视她吗？
So...You're just going to ignore her forever?
这是负责任的做法
It's the responsible thing to do.
这可不容易，
That's gonna be hard,
因为她正沿着楼梯走过来呢
'cause she's coming up the steps right now.
蛤？
What?!
哦！
Ohhh!
你好...康～妮
Hello...Connie.
史蒂文在家吗？
Is Steven home?
不
No.
他还好吗？我只是非常担心
Is he okay? I'm just really worried.
他一直不接电话
He hasn't been answering his phone.
发生了什么？
What's going on?
呃...
Uhh...
我-我不知道
I-I don't know.
我没法理解你们人类之间的关系
I don't understand your human relationships.
那么...呃...
So...Um...
再见
Goodbye.
史蒂文！
Steven!
史蒂文！！
Steven!!
史蒂文？
Steven?
史蒂文！
Steven!
你惹麻烦了？
Are you in trouble?
有什么不对吗？
Is something wrong?
我做错了什么吗？
Did i do something wrong?
为什么你要躲避我？
Why are you avoiding me?
史蒂文，我知道你在这里！
Steven, I know you're here!
你为什么要逃避我？！
Why are you hiding from me?!
"我们还是不要继续做朋友了"?
"I don't want to be friends anymore"?
史蒂文？
Steven?
我不能再跟你在一起了
I can't be with you anymore.
我有着自己的使命
I have a destiny.
当面跟我说啊！
Say it to my face!
说你不想继续当我的朋友啊！
Say you don't want to be friends anymore!
如果你能这么做--
If you can do that --
如果你能这么做，我就不再烦你了
if you can do that, I'll leave you alone.
而我只用回到没有朋友的日子
And I'll just go back to having no friends.
但除非你当面跟我说，我是不会相信的
But I won't believe it until you say it to my face.
那么？！
Well?!
我仍然想做朋友啊！
I still want to be friends!
史蒂文，你的眼睛！
Steven, your eye!
你到底遇上了什么？
What happened to you?
我不希望你担心
I didn't want you to worry about it.
我都担心的一整天了
I've been worried sick all day.
你以为我为什么要到这里啊？
What do you think I'm doing here?
我只是想保护你
I just wanted to protect you.
打住
Stop.
只要告诉我一切就好
Just tell me everything.
那么...青金石和铁石英在海底的某处
So...Lapis and Jasper are somewhere underwater.
没错，而橄榄石在飞船下坠的时候逃脱了
Yeah. And Peridot escaped while the ship was coming down.
她可能在任何地方
She could be anywhere.
那真是够消化一阵了
That is a lot to take in.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你呢？
你才是经历了这一切的人
You're the one that's been through everything.
我至少能做到倾听
The least I could do is just listen.
我不能要求你这么做
I can't ask you to do that.
我想这样，史蒂文
I want to, Steven.
我想成为你宇宙的一部分
I want to be a part of your Universe.
崽子！你在这啊
Kiddo! There you are.
哦，嘿，康妮，用送你回家吗？
Oh, hey, Connie. Do you need a ride home?
哦，爸爸
Oh. Dad.
你还好吧？
Are you doing okay?
我将忧虑排出体外了
I got it out of my system.
我又变回你的酷爹了
I'm back to being your cool dad.
若我能开始改变
If I could begin to be
到你期望的一半
Half of what you think of me
我愿付出我的一切
I could do about anything
我甚至能学着去爱
I could even learn how to love
如你
like you